Jialuo Yang

Research Interests

My research interest focuses on applying tangible interaction and sensing integration to improving human-computer symbiosis under the perspective of embodied cognition viewing human body as a multi-sensory system. I also study affective computing within the HCI through design and anthropological research.

Education

Georgia Institute of Technology Atlanta, GA

Aug 2022 - May 2024(Expected)

Master of Science, Digital Media

Hunan University Changsha, China

Sep 2018 - Jun 2022

Bachelor of Engineering, Industrial Design

Publications

[1] Tan, Hao, Xue Zhao, and **Jialuo Yang**. "Exploring the influence of anxiety, pleasure and subjective knowledge on public acceptance of fully autonomous vehicles." Computers in Human Behavior 131 (2022): 107187.

[2] Zhao, Xue, Jialuo Yang, and Hao Tan. "The Effects of Subjective Knowledge on the Acceptance of Fully Autonomous Vehicles Depend on Individual Levels of Trust." Cross-Cultural Design. Product and Service Design, Mobility and Automotive Design, Cities, Urban Areas, and Intelligent Environments Design: 14th International Conference, CCD 2022, Held as Part of the 24th HCI International Conference, HCII 2022, Virtual Event, June 26–July 1, 2022, Proceedings, Part IV. Cham: Springer International Publishing, 2022.

Research Experiences

Ubicomp Health and Wellness Lab Advised by Rosa Arriaga

Atlanta, GA, Jan - May2023

Research focuses on ImageScape therapeutic facilitation on mental health for veteran with PTSD

Digital World & Image Group Advised by Michael Nitsche, Ali Mazalek etc

Atlanta, GA, Jan 2023 -

Research focuses on tacit knowledge visualization and construction through tangible interaction and multi-sensory integration

iPED Studio & TUIIX Lab Advised by Wei Wang

Changsha, China, Oct 2021 - May 2022

Research focuses on remote control simulation and tactile interaction paradigm

iDi Lab Advised by Hao Tan

Changsha, China, Oct 2020 - May 2022

Research focuses on affective computing in public trust and acceptance of autonomous vehicles

Project Experiences

MR, Haptic Interaction & Interactive Agents

GaTech & HNU, Jun 2021

Handheld Device for MR haptic interaction through design through research, and rapid prototyping

User Researcher and UX Designer

Lemonbox, Jun - Aug 2021

Led user research and user experience design for digital product of health and wellbeing

User Researcher and Interaction Designer

DESIS NETWORK, Feb 2021 - Apr 2021

Led user research, ideation and design for service design for the elderly

User Researcher

China Telecom & HNU, Mar 2021 - Apr 2021

Conducted usability test, heuristic evaluation and walk through etc. for design iteration

Interaction Designer

Huawei & HNU, Nov 2020 - Dec 2020

Led user research, design and usability test for the client

Design Engineer

Microsoft Student Club - HNU, Oct 2019 - Nov 2019

Conducted the design and technological development for the whole project

Academic Services

Student Volunteer

UbiComp 2022